1. Name: Alana Zakroczemski

2. Your major and graduating year or Department: Computer Science Class of 2019

3. Telephone Contact: 716 957 0622

3. Name/title of submission: Visual L-System

4. Brief Description:
This visualization uses a Lindenmayer system in order to create a recursive fractal pattern. The process begins with an axiom, a string of symbols, which is then rewritten with a set of production rules. With multiple generations of the recursion, the square shape is formed, with slight overlap. L-systems started with studying growth patterns in nature, and has evolved into a strategic computer algorithm for design.